저기, 얘들아
Okay, guys, listen.
내일이 에밀리
결혼하는 날이잖아
Tomorrow, Emily gets married again.
오빠가 그거 생각나지
않도록 해야 돼
So try to really keep
Ross' mind off of it.
- 그게 좋겠다
- 알았어
Good idea.
Hey, man. What's up?
무슨 일 있어?
그냥 내일이 에밀리
결혼식이라서...
Just thinking about Emily
getting married tomorrow.
Oh, Ross! Look, look!
로스, 저걸 봐
저기!
What? Where?
뭐? 어디?
저쪽, 잘 보라니까
Right over there! There!
Look, look, look!
뭘 보라고?
-What am I looking at?
-Somebody help me out here.
지원 좀 안 할래?
- 얘들아
- 반가워요
Hey!
- 어서 와요
- 잘 지냈죠?
모니카, 어제 못 가서 미안해
게리랑 같이 있었어
Monica, sorry I didn't come by.
I was out with Gary.
순찰차 타고 돌아다녔거든
범죄 감시 및 예방활동
He let me ride around with him.
We saw and prevented crimes.
같이 순찰했어?
You got to go on a ride-along?
- 나도 그거 하고 싶은데
- 나도
-I want to go on a ride-along!
-Me too!
-Okay.
-Yeah! Me too!
- 좋아요
- 그럼 나도
진심이에요? 그쪽이?
Really? You?
그래요
Yeah.
- 너무 위험한데
- 나 위험 좋아해요
-Well, it's kind of dangerous.
-Well, I like danger.
- 그럼 오늘밤 괜찮아요?
- 네
-Okay, you guys free tonight?
-Yeah!
오늘밤?
야간순찰인 줄은 몰랐네
You didn't say
it was gonna be at nighttime.
The One With the Ride-Along
- 나 왔어
- 그래
마침 잘 왔다, 밀렸던
사진 좀 정리하려고
I'm so glad you're home.
We can finally organize these photos.
어머나
Oh, thank God!
Finally!
밀렸었구나
봐, 내가 종류별로 나눠놨어
I've broken them down
into categories.
명절, 생일, 스냅사진...
We got holidays,
birthdays, candids....
그걸 다시 주제별로 분류했거든
그러니까 예를 들어...
And I've cross-referenced
them by subject.
So if you're looking up, say...
...birthdays and dogs,
you get photo 152.
'생일'과 '개'를 찾으면
152번 사진이 나와, 어때?
See?
Oh, it's me and LePoo.
나하고 라푸잖아
Wow, I miss that dog.
정말 보고 싶다
'개'랑 '사망'으로도
이 사진이 나와
You can also find him
under "dog" and "dead."
Great. Thanks.
멋지다, 고마워
Hand me that other box of photos.
That's the last one.
좋아, 그 상자 이리 줘봐
그게 마지막이야
Oops.
웁스...
Sorry.
미안, 번호는 다 매겨 놨겠지?
Good thing you numbered them.
I hadn't.
안 매겼어
152번은 견본이라고!
Photo 152 was a prototype.
Honey, it's okay. It's okay.
얘, 괜찮아, 진정해
뭐 좀 마셔라, 마르카리타?
How about I fix you a drink?
Maybe a margarita?
Ross has the blender.
믹서가 오빠한테 있어
Everything's just falling apart.
제대로 되는 게 없네
괜찮아, 내가 믹서 가져올게
넌 재료나 준비해둬
It's okay. I'll go to Ross',
get the blender.
-You get the margarita stuff ready.
-All right.
그래, 키는 서랍에 있어
현찰도 좀 필요한데
His keys are in the drawer.
Also, I need some cash.
인출기에서 빼올까?
Want me to stop at the ATM?
아니, 오빠 집에
몇 장 굴러다닐 거야
No. While you're at Ross',
if you see any lying around.
-What?
뭐?
뭘? 나 그런 애 아냐
I don't do that.
사람 다루는 솜씨가
보통이 아니더군요
That was so cool, man.
The way you leaned on that guy.
점점 어두워지는걸
It is starting to get dark out there.
얼마나 겁에 질렸으면
묻지도 않은 걸 다 불죠?
He told you everything.
You cracked him.
어쨌든 피해자들은
말이 많은 법이죠
He was the victim.
They're usually pretty talkative.
Okay, but it is officially nighttime.
드디어 공식적으로
밤이 선포됐구만
- 그 '베리' 내가 들까요?
- 이건 '체리'예요
-Want me to grab the berry for you?
-It's called a cherry.
It's called
Chandler!
이게... 챈들러!
Okay, I got it.
됐어요
찾아냈다
This place makes the
best sandwich in the world.
이 집 샌드위치 맛은
세계 최고야
Does it have meatballs?
- 미트볼도 들었어요?
- 그럼요
Oh, yeah.
- 녹인 치즈와 마리나라 소스도?
- 넵
Melted cheese and marinara sauce?
Yep.
그런 거 내 차에선
먹지 맙시다
You can't eat that in my car.
Yeah, okay.
알았어요
Even though my tax dollars
paid for this car.
내 세금으로 산 차 아냐?
네가 낸 세금?
Your tax dollars?
그래, 알았다
Yeah, okay.
그 냄새 정말 좋다
Wow, that sandwich smells good.
내가 맡으라고 했냐?
Did I say you could smell it?
냄새도 맡으면 안 돼?
I can't smell it?
Half the taste is in the smell.
You're sucking up all the taste units.
맛의 절반은 냄새에 들어있는데
그걸 빨아들이면 어떡해
Okay, I'll give them back.
알았다, 돌려줄게
그 샌드위치가
뭐가 그리 대단한데?
What is so great about that sandwich?
좋아, 네 평생 최고의
섹스를 생각해봐
Imagine the best sex you ever had.
알았어
-Are you thinking about Monica?
-Yeah.
- 모니카 생각하지?
- 그래
What's that like?
어땠는데?
Please don't be from a real dinosaur.
Please, please.
진짜 공룡이면 안 되는데
이를 어째...
Please, please.
제발, 살려주세요...
"Made in Mexico."
Yes!
멕시코 산, 아싸!
Who would buy this?
돈이 썩어나는구나
Rach, it's me. Pick up!
레이첼, 나야
전화 받아
What's up?
그래, 왜?
I need a few more things
for the margaritas.
마르가리타 만들려면
몇 가지가 더 필요해
I need some salt,
some margarita mix and tequila.
소금이랑 마르가리타 믹스
그리고 테킬라
So all we had was ice?
우린 얼음밖에 없니?
얼음도 있는지 봐
See if he has ice.
알았어
Hello, Ross?
안녕, 로스?
나 에밀리야
It's Emily here.
너무 갑작스런 일이지만
나 내일 결혼해
I know this is out of the blue,
but I'm getting married tomorrow.
Well, maybe I am....
아마 하게 될 거야
자기 생각 많이 했는데
I keep thinking about you.
And I'm wondering if we made
a mistake giving up so fast.
우리가 너무 쉽게 서로를
포기한 것 같기도 하고...
Are you thinking about me?
자기도 내 생각해?
물론 아니겠지만
No, of course you're not.
But if you are, call me tonight.
만약 그렇다면 오늘밤
전화해 줘, 이만 끊을게
Okay, bye.
이젠 어디로 가죠?
Where we going?
자꾸 날 피하는 증인을
덮쳐볼까 하구요
This witness won't return my calls.
We'll surprise him coming home.
Surprise him? We're not gonna
make anybody mad, are we?
덮쳐요? 누굴 열 받게
하는 건 아니겠죠?
Come on, man.
왜 이래?
변호사 부르기 전에 그 흉악범
녀석을 살짝 주물러 줄 건가요?
You gonna squeeze the perp's shoes
a bit before he lawyers up?
흉악범이 아니라 증인이고
우린 그렇게 말하지 않아요
He's a witness, not a perp.
And no one talks like that.
맞아, 우린 그렇게 말 안 해
Yeah. No one talks like that.
-Oh, what, like you're Mr. Cop?
-I'm more cop than you two.
경찰나리 등장하셨네
- 너희보다야 훨 낫지
- 뭐가 나은데?
How do you figure that?
안 보여?
여긴 조수석이야, 됐어?
I'm in the front seat, okay?
난 개리의 파트너라고
I'm Gary's partner.
When you say "partner,"
it doesn't sound cop.
네가 파트너라고 하니까
경찰이 아니라 게이 같다
It sounds gay.
샘 나냐?
Jealous.
- 지금 잠복 중이에요
- 네, 알았어요
-Hey, we're undercover here.
-Oh, yeah. No problem.
-Ross!
-Sorry.
- 로스
- 미안해요...
There.
Hey, Gary. Who am l?
개리, 나 누구 같아요?
'집에 전화해'
Phone home.
Look at Officer Ross riding
back here with the visitors.
저런, 로스 경관님께서
뒷좌석엔 웬일이실까?
What's up with that, Serpico?
어떻게 된 거죠, 서피코 형사님?
"What's up with that, Serpico?"
Are you thinking about me?
No, of course you're not.
자기도 내 생각해?
물론 아니겠지만
But if you are, call me tonight.
만약 그렇다면 오늘밤
전화해 줘, 이만 끊을게
Okay, bye.
No.
말도 안 돼
I know!
누가 아니래
Thank God you were here.
We have to erase that.
네가 먼저 들어서 다행이다
지워버리자
What? We can't do that.
- 뭐? 그럴 순 없어
- 지워야 돼
We have to.
What if Ross hears that...
오빠가 저걸 듣고 전화해서 둘이
다시 만나면 어쩔래, 그걸 바래?
...and calls her back and
they get back together?
Is that what you want?
Ross back with that controlling...
의심 많고 제멋대로인
여자랑 잘되면 좋겠어?
...neurotic, crazy Emily?
The Emily that wouldn't let him see you?
- 오빠랑 널 갈라놓으려 했던?
- 안 되지
No! Oh, no, no.
God, no! He should not
get back with her.
안 돼, 그건 못 봐주지
다시 돌아가면 곤란해
I know that, you know that.
Even Ross knows that.
나도 알고 너도 알고
심지어 로스도 알지
But we have no right
to erase his message.
그렇다고 남의
메시지를 지우면 돼?
Look, I'm his sister and I love him.
I don't want to see him get hurt.
난 동생이야
오빠가 상처받는 거
보고 싶지 않아
Doesn't that give me
the right to control him?
이래도 오빠를 조종하면...
Help him?
도와주면 안 돼?
He's not the one who needs help.
도움이 필요한 사람은
로스가 아닌 것 같다
She's obviously unstable.
지금 에밀리는 상태가 불안해
식장에서 달아날 작정이라고
She's thinking about running
out on her wedding day.
Okay, fine. But look at the
position she's putting him in.
그거야 어찌됐든
오빠한테 이래도 돼?
And what's he gonna do?
그럼 오빠가 식장에 쫓아가서
판이라도 깨야된다는 거야?
Run over there on the wedding day
and break up the marriage?
Who would do that?
누가 그런 짓을 해?
Okay, fine. All right.
But that was different.
알았어, 하지만
그건 경우가 달랐어
Although it did involve
a lot of the same people.
다 한 사람 짓이지만
This is some twisted joke
she's playing on him.
이건 오빠를 갖고 놀려는
치사한 수작이야
You are crazy.
She sounded genuinely upset.
이성을 잃은 건 너야
이 목소리는 정말 절박하다고
I mean, listen.
들어보라니까
Your messages have been erased.
메시지가 삭제됐습니다
No!
아니 되옵니다
Well, that worked out well. Margarita?
어쨌든 해결됐네
마르가리타?
Okay, but we're safe, right?
Nothing bad's gonna go down.
우리 안전한 거 맞죠?
흉측한 일은 안 생기겠죠?
No. But that reminds me.
Sign this.
그럼요
말 나온 김에 서명들 해요
What is it?
이게 뭐죠?
It just says you can't sue
if you scrape your knee...
무릎이 까지고 머리가 날아가도
고소하지 않겠다는 서약서예요
...or get your head blown off.
빨랑 해, 나도 서명 좀 하자
Oh, hurry up. I want to sign that.
Here he comes.
저기 오는군요
What is he doing?
What the hell is he doing?
뭐하는 거지?
저건 또 뭐야
왜요? 뭔데요?
What is it?
- 괜찮은 거예요?
- 무슨 일이죠?
-ls everything okay?
-What?
들켰어요, 움직이지 말아요
쳐다보지도 말고
He sees us. Don't move.
And don't look at him!
Hey, it's okay.
It was just a car backfire.
괜찮아요
차 엔진 소리예요
저것 봐요
친구를 구하려고 하다니
Hey, look at that.
You tried to save your buddy.
You see that?
봤어요?
방금 그거?
You see what he did?
You okay, man?
괜찮냐, 임마?
응
...
Thanks, Joey.
고맙다, 조이
Hello?
이것들 보쇼!
Hi.
뭐?
You all right?
괜찮아?
We should go.
됐어, 가자
- 아니, 잠깐만
- 참, 그렇지
No, wait.
Oh, yeah. Right.
No. Monica.
아냐, 모니카...
Monica, we have to fix this.
이 일을 수습해야 돼
What can we do?
You erased the message.
이미 지웠는데 어떡할 거야?
Yeah, but maybe I could call his machine
and re-create the message.
내가 전화해서 똑같은
메시지를 남기면 어떨까?
All right, okay....
Hello, Ross, this is Rachel Emily.
안녕, 로스
나 레이첼... 에밀리야!
미치겠네
God, what is it with those two names?
이게 헷갈릴 이름이야?
I do so wanted to say
that I'm going to be getting married...
다름이 아니라
나 결혼하게 됐어
...to another British person.
어떤 영국 사람이랑...
And I'm having doubts and scones....
어쨌든 궁금한 게 있는데...
스콘도 있고... 환장하겠네!
-I can't remember what she said.
-Yeah, that's the problem with this plan.
무슨 말했는지 기억이 안 나
그게 이 작전의 허점이야
Rachel, come on. The message
is erased, there's nothing we can do.
메시지는 지워졌어
엎질러진 물이라고
He's never gonna find out.
오빠는 절대 모를 거야
내가 전해주면 되잖아
I could tell him about it.
If you want to be rational,
I can't argue with you.
그렇게 이성적으로 나오면
너랑 어떻게 얘길 하겠니
All right?
좋아, 맘대로 해
난 빠질래
Fine, tell him. I just don't
want to be a part of it.
에밀리라면 제발 똑같은
메시지를 남겨주세요
Maybe that's Emily leaving
the exact same message.
Hey, Ross, it's you. I just
want you to remember this feeling.
로스, 나 너야
지금 이 느낌 잘 기억해둬
You are lucky to be alive.
살아있다는 건 행운이야
So live every day to the fullest.
하루하루 최선을 다해 살도록
Love yourself, okay?
너 자신을 사랑하라 이거야
그럼 됐어
And also get stamps. Bye.
우표 꼭 사고, 안녕
Play that message for Emily,
and this problem goes away.
에밀리가 이걸 들으면
문제 깨끗이 해결인데
그렇지?
Right?
Anybody want to meet a hero?
영웅께서 납십니다
John Glenn is here?
존 글렌이 왔어?
No. Joey.
조이 말이야
Joey's never been in outer space.
조이는 우주에 나간 적 없는데
피비, 정말 굉장한 밤이었어
We had the most incredible night.
- 우리가 차 안에 있는데...
- 잠깐만요
-We're in the car
-Wait. Hold on.
-Hi.
- 안녕
- 어서 와
됐어요, 계속해요
Okay, go ahead.
좋아요, 차 안에 있었는데
빵! 하고 총소리가 난 거야
So we're in the car, and bang!
A shot was fired.
And Joey, with no regard
for his own safety...
근데 조이 이 녀석이
자기 몸을 날려서
...throws himself on me.
날 감싸 안지 뭐겠어
- 기특해라
- 엔진 소리였다네
My God!
It was a car backfire.
- 하지만 당시엔 몰랐지
- 그래, 난 몰랐어
But he didn't know that.
Yeah, I didn't know that.
진짜 총알이었을 수도 있잖아
It could just as easily
have been a bullet.
Ever think about joining the force?
We could use a guy like you.
조이, 경찰 될 생각 없어요?
우린 그런 사람이 필요한데
큰 소리에 펄쩍 뛰는 사람?
Who jumps at loud noises.
Wow. I could have died tonight.
나 오늘 죽을 수도 있었어
엔진 터진 차가
널 덮쳤다면!
Yeah, if the car that backfired
had run over you!
난 로스 녀석이 삶의 소중함
어쩌고 하기 전에 집에 가련다
I'm gonna go home, before Ross starts
rambling about his newfound respect for life.
정말 새삼 삶의 소중함을 느껴
I do have a newfound respect for life.
알아모시죠
Oh, my God!
Ross, I could have told you
you weren't gonna die today.
로스, 넌 오늘 안 죽어
What? You know when I'm gonna die?
내가 언제 죽을지 알아?
-You want to get some dinner?
-Sure.
- 저녁 먹으러 갈까?
- 좋지
참, 이거 알아?
You know what? If I heard a shot
right now, I'd throw my body on you.
지금 이 순간 총소리가 난다면
난 자기를 위해 몸을 던질 거야
Maybe we should walk
in a bad neighborhood.
정말? 그럼 우범지대로
산책이나 갈까?
- 좋아
- 그래
Okay.
Bye.
- 안녕
- 잘 가
Cut it out.
그만 좀 해라
I'd hate to save your life
and kick your ass on the same day.
같은 날 목숨도 구해주고
엉덩이도 걷어차 주랴?
야!
Why'd you take off?
- 왜 혼자 올라와?
- 산책 좀 하려고
Just going for a walk.
거실이든 어디든
Around the living room, whatever.
-ls something wrong?
-No. No, I'm just tired.
- 뭐가 잘못됐어?
- 아니, 그냥 피곤해서
산책하느라
You know, from the walk.
- 알았다
- 넌 로스한테 몸을 날렸어
You dove in front of Ross!
로스한테
Ross!
그것 때문이었구나
That's what this is about.
Oh, my God. You hate Ross!
맙소사, 너 로스가 싫지
I don't hate Ross.
- 로스가 싫긴!
- 아냐, 싫어해
Of course you do. I saved him.
You're mad at me. It adds up.
내가 로스를 구하니까 나한테
화가 났다, 앞뒤가 딱딱 맞잖아
You want Ross out of the picture.
로스를 제거하고 싶구나
What picture?
- 제거라니?
- 몰라, 하여간 정말 섬뜩하다
I don't know.
But I don't like what I'm hearing.
로스를 구한 건 백 번 잘했지만
진짜 총알이었다면 난 뭐냐고!
I'm glad you saved Ross in the car backfire.
But it could've been a bullet.
And you didn't try to save me.
You're upset because you think
I chose Ross over you.
널 두고 로스만 구했다고
서운하다 이거구나
무슨 소리, 넌 혼자서도
잘하니까 믿은 거지
No, I knew you could
take care of yourself.
You know? I mean, Ross needs help.
He's not "street" like us.
알잖아, 로스는 우리처럼
거친 사내가 아냐
You'd risk your life for Ross
before you would for me.
어쨌든 넌 나보다 로스를 위해
목숨을 걸겠다는 얘기잖아
That's the bottom line.
결론 나왔네
실은 그런 게 아냐
들어봐...
No, not exactly.
All right, look.
로스를 구하려고 했던 게 아냐
알았어?
I wasn't trying to save Ross.
Okay?
My sandwich was next to Ross.
내 샌드위치가 로스 옆에 있었어
됐냐?
All right?
I was trying to save my sandwich.
샌드위치를 구하려고 한 거라고
걔가 총 맞을까 봐?
From a bullet?
-I know it doesn't make much sense.
-"Much" sense?
- 물론 말이 좀 안 되지
- 좀 안 돼?
그건 본능이었어
그냥 달려들었다고
Look, it was instinct!
I just went for it.
샌드위치를 위해
목숨을 걸었다고?
You risked your life for a sandwich?
I know it sounds crazy...
물론 이상하게 들리겠지만
이 녀석은 세계 최고의
샌드위치라니깐
...but this is the greatest
sandwich in the world!
So you didn't choose Ross before me?
그니까 나 대신 로스를
택한 게 아니란 말이지?
물론이지!
어떻게 그럴 수 있나
No. I would never do that.
You're like my brother.
우린 형제나 마찬가진데
-Really?
-Yeah.
- 진짜?
- 당연하지
In fact, to prove how much
you mean to me....
그렇다면 내 마음을
증명해 보이겠어
Here.
받아
-Thanks.
-Easy, it's not a hot dog!
고맙다
살살 해
그게 무슨 핫도그냐?
맛이 어떤 것 같아?
How good is that?
See?
좋지?
What are you doing?
어허, 뭐하는 거야?
You're showing me how much
I mean to you.
네 마음을 증명한다며?
그니까 한 입이면 되지
With a bite.
꿈도 크셔
Jeez!
이제 오네
네가 여긴 웬일이야?
What are you doing here?
Hey, you know what?
넌 우리 집에 붙어살면서
이 정도는 새 발의 피잖아
You are in our apartment
all the time!
This is just a drop
in the bucket, mister!
It doesn't matter. The important
thing is that you're here.
아무래도 좋아, 네가 지금
여기 있다는 게 중요하지
내 소중한 친구가
여기 있다는 사실
You're my friend and you're here.
Okay, just a little scared.
What's going on?
살짝 무서워진다
무슨 일 있었어?
오늘밤 정말 놀라운
사건을 경험했어
The most amazing thing
happened tonight.
인생 종치는 줄 알았다니까
정말로 죽다 살아났지 뭐야
I thought my number was up.
I had an actual near-death experience.
뭐? 무슨 일인데?
What happened?
우리 오늘 게리하고
순찰 나갔던 거 알지?
We were on the ride-along with Gary
and somebody took a shot at me!
근데 누가 내게 총을 쐈어
Really?
정말?
알고 보니 엔진 소리였어
No. A car backfired.
난 진짜로 총에
맞은 줄 알았는데
But I thought somebody was taking
a shot at me. And, Rach...
...I survived!
이렇게 살아난 거야
생명의 소중함을
새삼 느끼게 됐어
And I was filled with
this great respect for life.
단 한순간도 헛되이
보내고 싶지 않아
I want to experience every moment.
I want to seize every opportunity.
내게 다가오는 기회를
하나도 놓치지 않겠어
모든 게 너무나 선명해졌어
I am seeing everything so clearly now.
Because a car backfired?
엔진 소리 덕분에?
Okay. Why are you here?
넌 여기 왜 왔는데?
이것도 그 짜릿한 경험의
일부가 될지는 모르지만
I don't know how this fits
into your whole "seizing" thing...
오늘 에밀리가 전화했어
...but Emily called you today.
-You talked to her?
-She left a message.
- 네가 받았니?
- 아니, 메시지를 남겼어
But it kind of got erased.
근데....
지워진 것 같아
I mean, there's something
wrong with your machine.
기계가 좀 이상해
- 에밀리가 뭐랬는데?
- 그게...
What did she say?
Something about having second
thoughts about the wedding...
이번 결혼에 대해 고민 중이고
헤어진 걸 후회하는 듯도 하고
...and did you guys make
a mistake breaking up?
And she wants you to call her.
너더러 전화해달래
Wow.
That was a good thing
that I told you, right?
내가 잘 전해준 거 맞지?
Yeah. Yes. Of course.
그럼, 물론이지
Okay, thank you. Thank you.
Because
그래, 정말 고마워
좋아, 모니카한테 가서
내가 옳았다고 말해야지
I'm gonna go tell Monica I was right.
걔 생각은...
중요하지 않아
Because she didn't want
Not important. Point is,
I was right. Your decision.
어쨌든 내가 옳았고
결정은 네 몫이야, 됐지?
Okay?
내가 옳았어
I was right.
Your decision.
- 결정은 네가 하는 거야
- 맞아
Right.
I guess I should call Emily.
에밀리한테 전화해봐야겠다
No, that's not the right decision.
얘, 그건 옳은 결정이 아냐
안 된다니까
로스, 왜 이래?
That's not right.
Ross, come on!
I mean...
...that woman made you miserable!
에밀리는 널 비참하게 만들었어
알아들었어?
너 정말 그걸 또 시작하고 싶니?
Do you really want
to get back into that?
들어봐, 만약 어제였다면
재고할 가치도 없었겠지만
Okay, look. Yesterday...
...I wouldn't have even
considered calling her back.
But my ex-wife calls
on the same day...
내가 죽음을 경험한 바로 그날
헤어진 아내가 전화를 한 건
...I have a near-death experience?
That's gotta mean something.
뭔가 의미가 있어
That was not a near-death experience.
That was barely an experience.
죽음의 경험 다 얼어죽었다
경험 축에도 못 드는 걸 갖고
You weren't there!
넌 거기 없었잖아
이건 붙들어야 할
기회인지도 몰라
Maybe this is something that
I'm supposed to seize, you know?
Okay. You know what?
좋아, 이거 알아?
Maybe this is not about seizing stuff.
이건 붙잡을 타임이 아니라
Maybe this is about escaping stuff.
달아날 타임이 아닌가 싶어
오늘 일을 되새겨 봐
잘 피해갔잖아...
Okay? Look at today.
I mean, you escaped...
...death.
죽음을
이건 다시 에밀리와 엮이는
불행을 피할 기회라는 거야
And maybe this is a chance
for you to escape...
...getting back together with Emily.
That does make sense.
그거 일리 있네
Because I do want to seize
some opportunity...
기회는 꼭 붙들어야 하지만
...but I really don't want
to see or talk to her.
에밀리는 보지도 말고
얘기도 하지 마라
Well, there you go!
- 바로 그거라니까
- 그래
아마도 오늘은...
Yeah, maybe today's just...
..."close call" day.
- '구사일생의 날'인가 보다
- 구사일생...
Hey, thanks, Rach.
- 정말 고맙다
- 별말을 다 하네
Oh, honey. No problem.
Wait, wait.
The message is blinking.
어라? 불이 깜박이는데?
안 지워졌나?
Maybe you didn't erase it.
Hey, Ross, it's you
- 로스, 나 너야
- 네, 알겠습니다
That's an old message.
Nobody needs to hear that.
철지난 메시지를
뭐 하러 듣고 앉았어
- 혹시 모니카 다녀갔니?
- 그래
-Hey, was Monica here?
-Yeah.
I want my money back.
- 내 돈 가져오라고 해
- 알았어
You probably need that
for stamps, right?
우표 살 돈인가 봐?
피비, 개리 총 맞은 적 있어?
Has Gary ever been shot at for real?
응, 한 번
Yes, once.
그래, 살짝
자기가 쐈대
A little.
He kind of did it to himself.
It's not really a good story.
재미없는 얘기야
I wonder how I'd react under fire.
And not backfire...
총탄이 쏟아지면
난 어떻게 나올까?
엔진 역화 말고 진짜 포화
...but heavy fire.
Like, if I was in a war.
예를 들어 전쟁터처럼
Man, I would be great in a war!
내가 전장에 나가면
정말 잘할 거야
I think I'd make
a fantastic military leader.
환상적인 지휘관이 될 텐데
I mean, I know I'd make general
before any of you guys.
남자애들 다 젖히고
맨 먼저 장군으로 진급할 걸
Before or after you were shot
by your own troops?
너희 부하들한테
총 맞는 게 아니고?
I know Joey would be in the foxhole
protecting all of us.
아마 조이는 참호 속에서
우릴 보호하고 있을 거야
그 참호를 샌드위치로
도배해놨다면
If the foxhole was
lined with sandwiches.
Yeah, hero sandwiches.
그래, 영웅 샌드위치
You all know I'm a pacifist, so I'm
not interested in war in any way.
알다시피 난 평화주의자라
전쟁 같은 건 관심 없어
But when the revolution comes,
I'll have to destroy you all.
하지만 혁명이 일어나면
너흰 나한테 다 죽었어
Not you, Joey.
조이 너만 빼고